That day the human race remembered
Fear that was dominated by them
I was trapped in a bird cage
[Uninteligible]
To me
Let's go home soon.
Why was this
I was sleepy until I got so sleepy
[Uninteligible]
Something else - I feel like I've been dreaming a
long time
What was it?
I can not remember
Ellen Why are you crying
[Uninteligible]
The wall was made by God
In the work of God
Anyone
[Uninteligible]
Not say
But it is unbelievable that tears come out
Once the uncle got to see it
[Uninteligible]
What are you crying about?
Was something sent to your side?
I'm crying
[Uninteligible]
I'm drinking it again.
How about you together?
work
Today is Montpe.
Because I'm here all day long apologize because I
apologize Haruna kicking my throat dry
It happened that drinks were mixed in drinks
It's a trivial matter
It's okay with that I can fight
throat
[Uninteligible]
It's the year when I broke the wall and came into
the city
[Uninteligible]
Do not suddenly remember me
I'm doing well I am a doctor
If they can break the wall  the sky is definitely
done
Such a thing never happened once in 100 years
It is the most dangerous time to feel at ease
My father was saying that
I forgot to say
Well certainly
The teacher made this town from a prevalent
disease
My head got up to the teacher
It's different
If you become an apprentice you can reinforce the
wall
I have a chance to see the roaring outside
I do not think I can do this 50 M wall in my
house
[Uninteligible]
You do not have the preparedness to fight with
them in the first place
Hey
[Uninteligible]
Let's no longer give a garrison a garrison and
let's eat all you can eat
That's bad  is not it?
Do it now.
What a soldier is doing is that it is the worst
time
It was better when we were stupid that we were
unavailable
Everyone can live peacefully
Even if you can not get out of the wall
You can live if you eat and sleep
But just as if
It's almost like a livestock
What a child is brave
You can do nothing  Erase none.
[Uninteligible]
It's a sweet guy
Do you want to enter Honkawa nursery school
You had better stop Ellen survey team
What's making a fool of your survey team
It is such a problem that it makes a fool of me
The search corps came back.
It's mys
[Uninteligible]
I will just come home
It was different from everyone.
It's a burger so it gets out of the wall so it's
gonna be like this
[Uninteligible]
Where's Pooh?
Moses' mother
Perfect
I could not get it back.
[Uninteligible]
It was helpful
Even if you do not meet directly
[Uninteligible]
In this survey
this time too
[Uninteligible]
Only one
I feel at home.
Totally
I got to feed them and feed them with our staff
[Uninteligible]
It's rich and chocolate  is not it?
Ellen
Feelings changed because I wanted to enter the
search corps
Helping of the castle
I do not need help
[Uninteligible]
About the Walls (1)
Humanity lives within three walls.
The outermost is Wall Maria.
The second, Wall Rose.
The innermost is Wall Sina.
[Uninteligible]
About the Walls (2)
Distance between each is roughly the same.
100km separate Maria and Rose.
130km separate Rose and Sina.
From Sina to the center is about 250km.
I'm home
Welcome back
[Uninteligible]
I tried hard today  unusually
My ears were red.
Lie proof
You got me handed to Mikasa
I'm leaving Higashiyama.
work
Raiichu Goddensai
It will take 23 days.
Ellen wants to enter the search corps
[Uninteligible]
What are you thinking?
I know how dead human beings went outside a woman
I know
[Uninteligible]
Why do you want to go outside
I want to know What is going on with the outside
world
I do not want to know anything and spend the
whole time in the wall.
Sony
If there was no one with no one here
The lives of dead people will be in vain so far
Soka
It's time for the ship
I'm about to go.
A little flowers
[Uninteligible]
What is Carla's quest for humanity?
It is not something that can be held down by
being told by someone
Ellen
When you return
Let me show you the cellar you kept secret for a
long time
truly
[Uninteligible]
Because it is useless
Investigating corps and becoming stupid
You're stupid.
I am a human being who can be fair
[Uninteligible]
Mikasa
That girl is so dangerous
When troubled  we can help each other
[Uninteligible]
2 year old male
Let's hit it if it's cheap
I do not want to do that
Well then it's the same level with you
[Uninteligible]
I admit that what I said is correct
I could only do what I could do without it
Is not it that it was executed?
[Uninteligible]
I ran away after seeing Mikasa
Sometimes
I will eat alone
Soka
So when you say that humankind should go to the
outside world
I wanted to be beaten up
[Uninteligible]
I just want to go outside Why can I see it with
white eyes
Because it was peaceful for 100 years just by
being in the wall
Do not invite them to go out and invite them into
the wall
They are children who are interested in the
outside world as a policy of the big government I
probably made it
I put my life on my mind but it is selfish.
Absolutely no good
No good
That's right You paid for your parents
I do not remember cooperating
How was it
I will not please it
I guess
surely
People who believe that inside this wall is safe
for everlasting
[Uninteligible]
Just because he was not destroyed for 100 years
Guarantee not broken today
There is nowhere
[Uninteligible]
What do you see?
Star Dragon
[Uninteligible]
Pilar
I can not run even if I get out of here
[Uninteligible]
Misato Yokado
I killed the giant
[Uninteligible]
I give back my love
That day the human race remembered
Fear that was dominated
Humiliation captured in bird cages
Fall of Sigunshina
Only human beings were allowed to preach and good
birds
Ellen only
I swear revenge on that small breast
I swear revenge
[Uninteligible]